government warns you to delete these
apps only because they are of this nature.
Today, smartphone is an integral part of your life.
Banking, online shopping, office
work and all other mobile
mediums are also very useful. In this situation, you
can download any such app on your phone and lose your
privacy, earn money, and personal
data. Currently, a government
agency has
issued a warning against these mobile apps which can create problems for you. From a
security point of view, it is
advisable to delete these apps from your phone immediately. You are
warned that
online fraudsters have become
more clever and active than before. Be
prepared for fake ones. It is easy to know that whether it is
real or fake, you can download any fake app and lose your personal information by
installing it on your phone. By just downloading any app, you can
gain complete control of your phone and in just a few
minutes, all the money from your bank account can disappear.
If you want to keep your phone and banking related data
safe, then definitely download this app and be alert.  Do
not install the app or
download the Anydex team's quick support app. If you do not
want to have any problem then please
submit it to your technical support team. But
cyber fraud is a practice that makes people
victims of fraud. Scammers
take complete control of the phone by remotely controlling it. They
operate your mobile and
steal your confidential data. The
government has advised you to be very cautious while using these apps. Generally, the
cyber fraud process starts with phone calls or
messages. The
criminals are considered to be bank employees,
customer care agents or government
officials and people do
not trust them. Here it is necessary to update your KYC.
Your refund is stuck or
your bank account is stuck. You are saying that you are
scared or greedy and you trap
ordinary people in your trap and help them here.  If
you install Aniex Team Viewer or Quick Support then you should
use it regularly and
delete it immediately from security point of view. If you install only very
important apps and
uninstall them immediately then you should
not share OTP with any bank, government department or
customer care person by calling any
remote access app or installing it on your phone. If you do
not get any
call or message list then trust it and
check it thoroughly and do
your normal work with your bank. If you are a normal person then you should
protect your financial condition by protecting your financial condition from cyber threats and
not harm your financial condition. Bureau
Report: Kanak Drishti